Max 猜猜Han在柜台做什么?
Max, guess what Han's doing at the counter?
反正不是在俯瞰柜台
Well, I know it's not towering over it.
他在为餐厅研制特色饮料
He's creating signature drinks for the diner.
我的建议是 在刨冰上加家常毒药
I suggested any household poison over shaved ice.
Han 这想法太蠢了
Han, this is a stupid idea.
这是Earl的想法
It was Earl's.
那这想法太棒了
Then it's genius.
是啊 我整个下午都在免费喝酒
Yep, I've been drinking all afternoon for free.
现在我只用顶级的酒
Now, I've used only top shelf liquor.
提问 谁帮你拿下来的?
Question: Who got it down for you?
第一款 "Max酒" 这只是杯威士忌
First up: "The Max". It's just whiskey.
酒加冰块(不断碰壁) 就像Max的工作
On the rocks, like Max's job.
不管我的酒是什么 我希望杯沿沾上盐
Whatever mine is, I want my rim salted.
当然可以
Of course you do.
"Earl酒"是一款什么都加的老式鸡尾酒
Earl's is an Old Fashioned with everything.
再给我倒杯"我"
Pour me another me.
我不想承认 但我很容易醉
I hate to say it, but I go down easy.
"Caroline酒"是装在稍微结霜的杯子里的柠檬甜酒
"The Caroline" is Lemon Schnapps in a slightly frosty glass.
是因为我那格蕾丝·凯利式的优雅举止吗?
Because of my cool, Grace Kelly kind of demeanor?
不是 是因为在卖酒的地方
No, because they had a sale on Lemon Schnapps
柠檬甜酒在促销
at Beverage Barn.
那里不用出示身份证吗?
Oh, they don't card there?
好了 那"Han酒"是什么?
Okay, so what's "The Han"?
沙滩上的"无性"酒吗?
A No Sex on the Beach?
我的是一款经典的摇和马提尼酒
Mine is a classic martini, shaken.
就像第一个看见你裸体的女人一样颤抖不停
Oh, like the first woman who saw you naked.
纠正
Correction.
是将要看见的
Will see you naked.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
破产姐妹花 第四季第14集
协调: 。沫   校对: 酱油影
翻译: morning  波特妹子  奥利奥  黄字君
Max 猜猜看 你迅速跑向厕所的两小时内
Max, guess what happened when you were running
发生了什么
to the bathroom real quick, for two hours.
你在柜台卖纸杯蛋糕
You worked the cupcake window while I went
而我去看了自由女神像
to see The Statue of Liberty.
她的头正在被翻新
Her head was being renovated.
城里的每个人都在工作
Everybody in this town is getting work done.
我卖掉了最后一件纸杯蛋糕T恤!
I sold our last cupcake tee!
我们卖掉的比罗伯特·德尼罗
We've sold out more than Robert De Niro
在他职业生涯的最后20年里卖的还多
in the last 20 years of his career.
"老大靠边闪" 逊毙了
Well, Analyze This, Focker.
"老大靠边闪" 罗伯特·德尼罗主演的电影
我注意到 我们上周快要缺货了
I noticed we were running low last week,
所以我又进了点货
so I ordered more.
我怎么没早发现那些呢?
How did I not notice those sooner?
哦 很可能是因为我上次往里看的时候
Oh, probably because the last time I looked in there,
有只老鼠正和蟑螂嘿咻
there was a rat having sex with a cockroach.
告诉你 它们还在约会
You know, they're still dating.
真的吗? 我还以为是一夜情
Really? I thought it was a one time thing.
我猜你一旦上了老鼠 就永不回头了
Well, I guess once you go rat, you never go back.
go rat出自DOTA术语"只推塔 不团战"
谢谢你进了这些货 我最近都忙着
Thanks for ordering these, I've just been so busy
准备Sophie的告别单身派对
with Sophie's wedding shower.
是啊 我们为什么这么尽心尽力?
Yeah, why are you working so hard?
又不是什么大事
It's not a big deal.
我还帮我妈告别过单身呢
I threw my mother a shower once.
不对 等等 我是直接把她扔到雨里过
No, wait, I threw her in a shower once.
Max 你真的不该这么抱怨了
Max, you really need to start making more of a fuss.
这是为了Sophie 这对她很重要
It's for Sophie, it means a lot to her,
而且她还有枪
and she has a gun.
单身派对是傻姑娘的事情
Well, showers are stupid girl things
而这条汉子不想参与
that this guy wants no part of.
嘿 姑娘们!
Hey, girls!
看 我在给你们的纸杯蛋糕做广告
Look. I'm advertising your cupcake business.
你是在做广告 但不是我们的纸杯蛋糕广告
You're advertising something, but it's not our cupcakes.
我给我们楼的住户发放了免费T恤
I gave out free T-shirts to our building.
我在每家每户门口都留了一件
I left one by everyone's door.
Sophie家两件 Sanchez家16件
Two at Sophie's, 16 at the Sanchez's.
大概有六个孩子得共穿一件
So about six of the kids will have to share.
真有趣 现在我们的T恤
Interesting. Now our shirts are available at both Rodney,
在高档的曼哈顿时装店"Rodney"
the high-end Manhattan boutique,
和一栋永远飘着汽油味儿的公寓楼里
and an apartment building that always smells
都能拿到
a little like gasoline.
请不要再聊些跟我无关的事情了
Well, please stop talking about things that aren't me.
姑娘们 你们准备好
Now girls, did you get the cake
明天我的单身派对上的蛋糕了吗?
for my wedding shower tomorrow?
哦 我还要做个蛋糕吗?
Oh, was I supposed to make a cake?
我完全没有为这个派对做任何事情
I've literally done nothing for this shower.
我连澡都没有洗
I haven't even taken a bath.
不 我不要这里的蛋糕
Oh, no, I'm not getting my cake from here.
不行 这是我的婚前派对
No, this is my bridal shower.
对 我要从Baskin Robbins冰淇淋店买点经典甜品
Yeah, I want to get something classic from Baskin Robbins
还有Dunkin甜甜圈
that's also a Dunkin' Donuts.
他们现在把这两样混搭了?
They mix those two now?
斯通纳(主持)的梦想成真了
It's a Stoner's dream come true.
我想让我们的公寓好看一点
I tried to make our apartment look nice.
我甚至挪动椅子来遮住污渍
I even moved a chair to cover a stain,
但椅子下面更脏
but what was under the chair was so much worse.
我想说的是 请不要开枪打我们
I guess what I'm saying is, please don't shoot us.
我没期待它有好多看
Well, I don't expect it to look that good.
你们不能给猪戴上大礼帽
I mean, you can't put a silk hat on a pig.
我知道 是因为我试过一次
And I know, 'cause I tried once.
Max! 天啊! 你干了什么?
Max! Oh, my God! What have you done?
我觉得我不喜欢草莓馅的
I realized I don't like a strawberry center.
但我不会为此揍自己一顿
And I am not going to beat myself up about it.
我让你去拿皱纸带
When I told you to get crepe paper streamers
装饰下派对的时候 我说的是粉红色 不是黑色
and decorate for the shower, I meant with pink, not black.
这是Sophie的单身派对
It's a wedding shower for Sophie,
不是"魔鬼圣婴"的洗礼会
not a baby shower for Rosemary's Baby.
什么? 我跟你说了 我不会做小女生的事情
What? I told you, I don't do girl things.
像挂粉红彩带 或者坐着尿尿
Like hang pink or sit when I pee.
我正好提到了"挂粉红彩带"这项
Which, coincidentally, I refer to as "hanging pink."
天啊 什么味道?
My God, what is that smell?
这里真的有什么东西坏了
Something's really gone bad here.
包括我们的生活
Besides our lives.
这是波兰食物
It's the Polish food.
我想其中有根香肠是用穿过的人字拖做的
I think one of those sausages is made of old flip-flops.
已经有人来了?
Someone's here already?
波兰人都这么早吗?
Are Polish people always early?
这是什么我不知道的刻板印象吗?
Is that a stereotype I don't know about?
我滴个乖乖!
Oh my God!
我的单身派对?
A wedding shower for me?
要是早知道 我就好好打扮一番了!
I mean, if I had known, I would have dressed!
Sophie 你确实知道啊
Sophie, you did know.
我知道 我提早下来练习一下入场
I know. I came down early to practice some entrances.
现在准备排练入场方式二
Now get ready for entrance number two.
你能想象第二种入场啥样吗?
Are you ever ready for entrance number two?
谁啊?
Who is it?
亲娘啊!
Oh my God!
简直不敢相信
I can't believe it.
哦 今天是我的单身派对啊
Oh, it's the day of my wedding shower.
还有什么比这更美好的?
Could anything be more wonderful?
我好感动 好惊讶
I was moved, I was surprised.
比圣经还要喜欢
I liked it better than the Book.
现在 进来指出哪些是波兰食物
Now, come on in here and identify some of this
这样我就知道晚上什么不能吃了
Polish food so I can know what I'm not eating tonight.
哦 不 我派对上不吃东西
Oh, no. I'm not eating at my shower.
我在假装自己有进食障碍症
I'm pretending I have an eating disorder
这样大家就以为我拥有一切了
so everyone will think that I have it all.
我觉得你会很开心的
I think you're going to be happy.
我有很多好玩的单身派对游戏
I have lots of fun shower games,
从"谁最了解Sophie"开始
starting with "Who Knows The Most About Sophie?"
哦 这个肯定我赢
Oh, I'll win that one.
是啊
Yeah.
Sophie得上厕所了
And Sophie's got to tinkle.
看到没? 这事都知道肯定赢
See? I'm a shoo-in.
哦 哦 天啊
Yeah. Oh. Oh, my gosh.
黑色厕纸
Black toilet paper.
做得不错 两位妞儿
Oh, nice touch, girls.
嗯 我就喜欢擦完还不知道的神秘感
Yeah, I love the mystery of not knowing when you're done.
联邦调查局! 开门!
FBI! Open up!
联邦调查局? 我没请他们啊
The FBI? I don't think they RSVP'd.
哦 肯定是来抓我的
Oh, that's got to be for me.
我啥也没干
I didn't do it.
而且告诉你 纽瓦克的那件事
And just so you know, the statute of limitations is up
已经过了诉讼时效了
on that Newark thing.
我不是来抓你的 小姐
I'm not here to arrest you, miss.
这下好了 抓我来的
Great, it's me.
Max 我都说盗印电影是犯罪了
Max, I told you pirating movies was a real crime.
这下我要因为"五十度灰"进局子了
Now I'm going to jail for Fifty Shades Of Grey.
总得有人进去
Someone should.
我听到了 你不是我想象中的
I hear you, not the Christian Grey
Christian Grey(五十度灰女主人公)
I'd pictured.
我是联邦调查局的Drake探员
I'm Agent Drake with the FBI.
不用担心 但是你们楼里有个男人
Nothing to get upset about, but there's a man in your building
在他的公寓里扣留了三个女人
who's been holding three women hostage
做人质有数月了
in his apartment for months.
嗯 这听起来才对
Yeah, that sounds about right.
现在 其中一个被关押的今天逃出去
Now, one of the captives escaped today
报警了
and alerted authorities.
哦 肯定是我在大厅里遇到的
Oh, that must have been the lady I passed
尖叫的那位女士
screaming in the hall.
怎么了? 这栋楼里"人质"和"精神错乱"之间
What? There is a fine line between "hostage"
还是有区别的
and "off your meds" in this building.
所以 特警队要进来
So, a SWAT team is going in
解救楼上剩余的两位
for the other two still upstairs.
但我们首先要清空楼内
But we need to evacuate the building first.
所以请吧
So let's go.
好的 我能先收拾下东西吗
All right, can I just put a few things away first.
你知道 如果有警察要进来的话
You know, because I want the place to look nice
我希望家里看起来干净些
if there's going to be police in here.
听着 小姐 不过你家里藏了什么毒品
Look, miss, whatever drugs you're hiding in here,
我完全不在乎
I couldn't care less.
我们得马上出去
We need to get out now.
你知道吗 你完全是我的理想型
You know, you're just my type of guy.
你不介意我用药 而且已经在家门口了
You don't mind my drug use and you're already here.
哦 对味儿!
Oh, yeah!
你们还请了脱衣警察来我的单身派对?
You girls ordered a cop stripper for my bridal shower?
哦 新娘这就来了!
Oh, here comes the bride all right!
来啊
Come on. Yeah.
嗯 看到没? 他喜欢我
Yeah, see? Look, he likes me.
真不敢相信我住的楼里
I cannot believe I live in this building
竟然有男人做这么可怕的事
with a man who would do something so awful.
当然 也不敢相信我竟然住在这样的楼里
Also, cannot believe I live in this building.
你知道我觉得是谁吗?
You know who I think it is?
一身猫味却不养猫男
Smells Like Cats But Has No Cats.
是吗? 他看起来不像个行动派啊
Really? He doesn't seem like a go-getter.
我觉得是三个乳头没鼻子男
I think it's Three Nipples No Nose.
三个乳头没鼻子男? 他人很开朗啊
Three Nipples No Nose? He's a delight.
Sophie 你不难过吗?
Sophie, isn't this upsetting?
当然了
It sure is.
那个脱衣警察就是不肯脱裤子
I couldn't get that stripper cop to take his pants off.
嘿 快看 我的派对客人们来了
Hey, look, there's some of my shower guests.
快看
Oh, look.
看到没? 那个是我的朋友Natalya
And see? That one's my friend Natalya.
跟你们提过的那个
The one I told you about.
没错 瞧那多余的皮肤
Yeah, there's all that extra skin.
天啊 你真没夸张
Ew. You were not exaggerating.
那皮肤是天生的
She was born with all that skin.
她整个高中都得
She had a chip clip on her back
在背上夹个夹子
all through high school.
嗯 我知道楼上的家伙真让人扫兴
Yeah, I know that guy upstairs is a real bummer,
但你知道什么有帮助吗?
but you know what would help?
要是我能开礼物的话
If I could open my presents.
没错
Yeah.
哦 不!
Oh, no!
警察不让她们过来!
The fuzz isn't letting them through!
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.
不公平 他们几分钟前还放一个男的进来了
No fair, they just let a guy in here a few minutes ago.
我朋友们不是炸弹搜寻犬
Just 'cause your friends aren't bomb-sniffing dogs,
就不让进吗? 切!
they can't get in? Boo!
听着 姐妹们 把你们的礼物递给条子
Hey, look, ladies, pass your presents up to the cops.
条子 把我的礼物递给我
Cops, pass my presents to me.
等等 Sophie 在你打开它们前
Wait, Sophie, before you open them,
我真得很想记下是谁送的礼
I really want to write down who got you what.
还有 留着那条漂亮的丝带 我给你做顶蝴蝶结帽!
And save that pretty ribbon, I'm gonna make you a bow hat!
看看你
Look at you.
有个疯子绑架了三名无辜女性
Making lemonade out of a maniac
你还能这么苦中作乐
holding three innocent women hostage.
一张礼品卡
Oh, a gift card.
把它寄回去
Oh, send it back.
Sophie 换做我们就会收下它
Sophie, we would've taken that.
虽然不知道它的用处
I don't know what is was for,
但我就知道 我们会收下它
I just know that we would've taken it.
不 我要把它寄回去
No, I'm sending it back.
我要的是礼物 不是多一份差事
I want a gift, not another errand.
好吧 我不太喜欢这个包装 但...
Oh, yeah, not in love with the paper, but...
还是等打开后再做定论吧
well, I'll wait till I open it to judge.
嗨 打扰一下
Hi. Excuse me.
打扰一下?
Excuse me?
我是Maria Alonso-Gonzalez
I'm Maria Alonso-Gonzalez.
能请两位女士对着镜头
Could you ladies talk to Channel 2
谈谈今晚这里的骇人发现吗?
about tonight's disturbing discovery?
- 没门  - 当然
- No.  - Yes.
只管跟着我和我的商业头脑走
Just go with me and my business savvy.
是的 Maria Alonso-Gonzalez 我们可以回答几个问题
Yes, Maria Alonso-Gonzalez, we can answer a few questions.
有任何迹象表明 你所居住的楼房里暗藏
Were there any signs at all that something of this nature
此类性质的犯罪吗?
was going on in your building?
我们只是希望 住我们楼里的这个变态
We just hope they bring this sick freak
能被绳之于法
in our building to justice
好让我们回到"Max自制纸杯蛋糕店"继续工作
so that we can return to work at Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
转拍大门 他出来了
Get on the door. Here he comes.
这人是谁? 谁是这个变态?
Who is it? Who is this sick freak?
不是我
It's not me.
是我吗?
Is it?
我不太确定 我被指控了什么?
I'm not sure, what are the charges?
同是变态 各不相同
Different sick freak.
嘿 Rula Uma Greta 看啊
Hey, Rula, Uma, Greta, look.
就是这人
This is him.
我的未来夫君
This is the groom-to-be.
忘了楼上那个家伙吧
Forget about the guy upstairs,
这才是货真价实的床上狂魔
this is the real maniac in the bedroom.
就是他?
That's him?
啤酒肚运动裤男?
Beer Belly Gym Shorts?
- 怎么都猜不到  - 糟了
- Never would've guessed.  - Oh, no.
他穿着我们的衣服
He's wearing one of our shirts.
为什么?
Why?
为什么? 他为什么要穿中号的?
Why? Why is he wearing a medium?
哦...
Oh...
没人会在意那个的
I mean, nobody's gonna see that.
警察已经逮捕了嫌疑犯
Police have just apprehended the suspect
而现在每个人心中的困惑是
and the question on everyone's mind is,
Max自制纸杯蛋糕店究竟和此事
"What does Max's Homemade Cupcakes
有什么牵连?
have to do with this?"
我们无可奉告
We have no comment.
也没有未来和除臭剂
Or future, or deodorant.
所以别来烦我们!
So leave us alone!
他们怎么知道我们在这破地方工作
How did they find out we work in this dump,
旁边靠着另外那个破地方?
next door to the other dump?
我说完才意识到 我们的职业生涯
As I'm saying it, I realize our career
全搭在这两破地方了
is made up of two dumps.
听起来像是我们的职业生涯咖啡喝多了
Sounds like our career has been drinking too much coffee.
报纸上通篇在报道这事
The story is all over the paper.
他们称那些女性为"纸杯蛋糕俘虏"
They're calling those ladies "The Cupcake Captives,"
称那家伙为"纸杯蛋糕绑匪"
calling that guy "The Cupcake Captor,"
还称整个事件为"纸杯蛋糕大浩劫"
and calling the whole thing "The Cupcake Catastrophe."
但你们不用担心这事会损坏你们
But you needn't worry about it reflecting badly
纸杯蛋糕生意的声誉
on your cupcake business.
糟了 这事还上时尚专区了
Oh, no. It's even in the fashion section.
上面有我们衣服的图片 还写着
There's a picture of our shirts and it says,
"不要穿这个 永远不要"
"What not to wear, ever."
好吧 各位冷静一下
Okay. Everybody calm down.
我多半是在说自己
I'm mostly talking to myself.
媒体就喜欢兴风作浪
The media is just going to do its thing.
我之前也被头条诽谤过
I've been slandered in the headlines before.
被称为"庞氏骗局公主" "破产芭比"
I was called "Ponzi Princess," "Bankrupt Barbie."
回首往事 那些竟是最美好的时光
Looking back, those were the best of times.
各位好啊 我刚打算递一盘
Oh, hello. I was just about to take a tray
Max和Carolines酒招待我的记者朋友们
of Max and Carolines out to my reporter friends.
抱歉 你可以拿这些Max和Carolines酒
Sorry, you can give those Max and Carolines
招待Max和Caroline
to this Max and Caroline.
嗨 各位亲
Hi, everybody.
哦 我抑郁极了
Oh, I'm depressed.
瞧 连你们都看得出 因为我只戴了一半的假发
See, you can tell 'cause I'm only wearing half my hair.
姐妹们 我在你们家门前发现了这个箱子
Girls, I found this box outside your door.
我当时还以为这是单身派对礼物
And I was hoping it was a shower present.
因为那些自私的人质姑娘毁了我的大好日子
Since those selfish hostage girls ruined my special day.
天啊 我都没能拿到那顶蝴蝶结帽
Oh, man. I didn't even get a freakin' ribbon hat.
你想要我用警示带做的抹胸吗?
Do you want the tube top I made out of the police tape?
我管它叫"警示抹胸"
I'm calling it a tape top.
专利申请中
Patent pending.
好啦 各位
Come on, you guys.
这不关我们的事
This isn't about us.
我们要理性看待这事
We need to put this all in perspective.
我们都没事 健健康康的 还有...
We're all safe, and healthy, and...
天啊 正当我觉得不能承受更多时
Oh, my God, just when I can't take anymore,
更多的不幸就来了
here comes anymore.
"我们要退还你们T恤剩余的存货
"We are returning the remainder of your T-shirt stock.
我们Rodney品牌不愿与你们的产品有牵连
Our Rodney brand cannot be associated with a product
因为它涉及了一项正在进行中的刑事调查
at the center of an ongoing criminal investigation.
我们的合约就此作废"
Consider our contract null and void."
真是让人震惊
This is so shocking.
Max 你竟然识字?
Max, you can read?
看来你只是不肯把特价菜单报给客人
So you just didn't want to tell people the specials.
真是难以置信
I can't believe this.
我们盼了这么久 希望有事发生在
We waited so long for something to happen
我们的纸杯蛋糕T恤上
to our cupcake t-shirts.
为什么是他?
Why that guy?
而且是正好在他不想穿那件
And on the one day he chooses to not wear
写着"拉我手指"T恤的时候
his "Pull my finger" shirt.
我是Maria Alonso-Gonzalez 在Max自制纸杯蛋糕店...
This is Maria Alonso-Gonzalez, reporting to you live...
Max 你在干什么? 他们会看到我们的
Max, what are you doing? They'll see us.
- 现场为您带来的报道  - 他们看不到的
- From Max's Homemade Cupcakes.  - No they won't,
因为所有的摄像机都对着Han
Because all the cameras are on Han right now.
你能谈一下 Max自制纸杯蛋糕店背后的
Can you talk a little bit about the women
两位女性的故事吗?
behind Max's Homemade Cupcakes?
就这么说吧 Max和Caroline
Well, let's just say Max and Caroline
对工作过敏 就像是
are allergic to work, much in the same way
Dilbert对周一过敏一样
Dilbert is allergic to Mondays.
继续 Maria Alonso-Gonzalez
Moving on, Maria Alonso-Gonzalez,
您想不想来威廉斯堡餐厅
would you care to come into The Williamsburg Diner,
贝德福德大道6355号
6355 Bedford Avenue,
营业时间从早上八点到凌晨两点
open 8:00 A.M. till 2:00 A.M.,
来喝一杯我们的招牌饮料"纸杯蛋糕绑架小宇宙"?
for our signature drink: The Cupcake Captive Cosmo?
至于先生们 想来杯"纸杯蛋糕绑架鳕鱼"?
And for you gents, The Captive Cape Cod?
嘿 把那些纸杯蛋糕从垃圾桶里拿出来
Hey, get these cupcakes out of the garbage.
我得给Han的尸体腾出点位子
I need to make room for Han's body.
我要留着他的头来警告其他想要惹我们的人
I'm keeping the head as a warning to others who cross us.
我们得找做新闻的人安排一次采访
We need to take back our t-shirts' image
拯救一下我们T恤的形象
by setting up an interview with the news.
我说"我们"的时候 我是说你
And by "we," I mean you.
听着 如果我在上"执法先锋"节目时得了一个教训的话
Look, if I learned one thing from my time on Cops,
那就是我得花三秒整才能跳过一个篱笆
it's that I can hop a fence in three seconds flat.
如果得了两个教训的话 那就是摄像机
If I learned two things, it's that the camera
让我看上去有罪
makes me look guilty.
特别是那个在香蕉共和国里的监控录像机
Especially when it's a security camera at Banana Republic.
我可不能去
I can't do it.
这个世界不能知道Caroline Channing
The world can't know that Caroline Channing
和另外一场备受瞩目的犯罪相关
is involved in another high-profile crime.
而且还一点都没有保养她的指甲
And hasn't kept up her nail maintenance, like, at all.
好吧
Fine.
如果我在上"执法先锋"节目时得了三个教训的话
Because if I learned three things from Cops,
就是最好在还没有被剥光之前趁早投降
it's that it's best to surrender early and not naked.
我们很感激你们抽出时间来和我们谈
We really appreciate you taking the time to talk to us.
如果你们想谢我
If you really want to thank me,
能不能给我的脸上打点马赛克?
how about I get some pixels up over my grill?
有几个小孩在找我 我不想帮他们
I got some kids looking for me and they don't need the help.
这个我们做不到
We don't have the capability to do that.
这是电视直播
This is live TV.
那么那种变声装置怎么样?
How about one of those voice distorting machines?
就是那种能把我的声音变得像大胖变形金刚的
You know, make my voice sound like a fat Transformer.
呃 没有
Um, no.
没问题
No problem.
我会自己搞定的
I'll take care of that myself.
以前也干过
Been in this sitch before.
好吧 3秒 2秒...
All right, in 3, 2...
晚上好 在威廉斯堡...
Good evening. In Williamsburg...
Max 如果你需要我的话 我就在这里
Max, I'm right here, if you need me.
我能搞定
I got this.
这个因为令人震惊的"纸杯蛋糕绑架案"而声名狼藉的地方
Now infamous in the shocking "Cupcake Captives" story.
我和店主Max Black在一起
I'm here with the owner, Max Black.
嗨 Maria
Hi, Maria.
Max  你知道Richard Griffin是Max自制纸杯蛋糕店
Max, how upset were you to see that Richard Griffin
最大粉丝的时候 你烦恼吗?
was Max's Homemade Cupcakes' biggest fan?
我非常不高兴
I was really upset.
好吧 嗨 我来吧
Okay, hi. Stepping in.
Max看来是因为这一切
Max is clearly so upset by all this
难过得都疯了
that she's lost her mind.
我真的需要她的时候就掉链子
The one time I really needed her, anyway.
嗨 Maria
Hi, Maria.
你的公司和一个在家里
How will your company's reputation recover
囚禁了三个女人的男人做生意
from doing business with a man
你们的名声要怎么恢复?
who held three women in his apartment against their will?
听着 人们会做一些可怕的事
Look, people do terrible things.
还是穿着衣服在做
And they do them wearing shirts.
这并不代表衣服是邪恶的
That doesn't make the shirt evil.
如果一件衣服犯了罪 那就把它关起来吧
Now, if a shirt commits a crime, lock it up.
我不会和你争论的
You'll get no argument from me.
- 我需要回来吗?  - 我能搞定
- Should I jump back in?  - I got this
好吧 呃 我们时间到了
Okay, yeah. That's all the time we have.
- 谢谢  - 嗯哼
- Thank you.  - Mm-hmm.
谢谢
Thank you.
Caroline 谢谢你为我办单身派对
Caroline, thank you for trying to throw me a shower.
我是说 我们一直不是什么亲密的朋友
I mean, we were never really friends or close.
是啊 我逃跑是因为你走向
And yeah, I run away when I see you heading towards
那个信箱的时候 我...
the mailboxes the same time as me...
别谢我了
Please stop thanking me.
嘿 想来我们家吗?
Hey. Want to come to our place?
那些猪蹄还没坏呢
Those pig feet haven't gone bad.
我猜是猪蹄 很难辨别
I guess. It's hard to tell.
是啊 最美味的肉就在指甲下面
Yeah. The best meat's under the toe nails.
是吗?
Is it?
惊喜
Surprise.
天啊 这是怎么回事?
Oh, my God, what's all this?
天啊 我太吃惊了
Oh, no. I'm so surprised.
我这次是真的很吃惊
No, I really am this time.
- 我也是  - 我也是
- So am I.  - Me, too.
在我尝到这个香肠之前 我还以为吃过的
Until this sausage, I thought the grossest thing
最难吃的东西是甘蓝呢
I'd ever eaten was kale.
天啊 真不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe it.
还有什么能比这更好吗?
Could anything be more wonderful?
Max 真不敢相信你做了这件事
Max, I can't believe you did all this.
我以为你回家是干你平时不开心的时候
I thought you came home to do what you usually do
经常干的事呢
when you get depressed.
喝醉酒 然后对着台阶上的人竖中指
Get drunk and throw the finger at people from the stoop.
台阶没有 不过我的确是喝醉了
No stoop. But I am drunk.
你以为我清醒的时候能做这种事?
You think I could've done this sober?
我只是觉得 我们身边的事最近那么黑暗
I just figured, with everything around us being so black lately,
我们需要一点粉红色
I thought we needed a little pink.
你说得对
You're right. We did.
因为我们的T恤生意是完了
'Cause our t-shirt business is over.
我们还得还银行贷款 怎么办?
And we still have to pay off that bank loan. Now what?
我们会找到办法的 我们都能成功
We'll figure something out. We always do.
嘿 姑娘们 快来
Hey, girls, come quick.
我们要来玩"猜猜Sophie最爱的体位是什么"
We're gonna play "Guess Sophie's Favorite Sex Position"
哦!
Whoo!
是后背位 还得看着"逍遥法外"
It's on all fours, watching How To Get Away With Murder.
看到了吧? 我就说我会赢的
See? I told you I was gonna win.
生活又变黑暗了
And it just got black again.
是啊 非常黑暗
Yeah, real black.
这是湿的 Max 你已经吃过这个了吗?
This is wet. Max, did you already eat this?
我跟你说我不喜欢草莓糖
I told you I don't like a strawberry centre.
我才不会打自己一顿呢
I am not gonna beat myself up about it.